(Watch on KonFlix.vip)
Where's the former Supremo now?
He's dead.
They're always monitoring us, Zein.
Zein
if something bad happens to me
Please
tell Supremo that I'm sorry.
Foundation Day!
Free Bloody Night later.
No weapons.
No exemptions.
It's nice to be in peace, not hell.
I hope the gangs won't cause trouble.
Welcome to
Hell University's
Mr. and Ms. Face of the Year!
you can look at me as
much as you need.
Eyes on me only.
Don't look at anyone else.
Be with me.
I will make you my world.
Isn't that the mark of
the Black Blood Gang?
Why was she killed by the BBG?
Where are you going again?
This is between me and Matt.
Zein...
Zein
This is just the beginning.
Zein, what is it?
What's wrong?
What?
Are you involved in Celine's murder?
Answer me, Matt!
Zein
What did you have to do with it?
Zein, I didn't have anything to do-
Liar!
I trusted you, Matt.
How can you do this to us?
To me?
Zein, I'm not lying to you.
Zein, I'll never turn on you.
Then why?
Why did you have to join
the Black Blood Gang?
So you'll have more allies?
To assure you won't die?
Isn't having us as allies enough?
There's a storm brewing, Matt.
Only a few of us know about it.
What is it?
There's a war coming
War?
Yes
and we're looking for dependable allies.
People who are smart enough
to choose the winning side.
Can I trust you?
Yes.
Good.
I need to know more.
What's the plan?
I'll tell you in the right time.
For now
I just need to know
where your loyalty stands.
Wow.
Dramatic.
By the way
when you said you wanted power...
what did you mean by that?
I need power.
The power to protect my friends.
And I know I can't do that on my own.
That's so sweet
and pitiful.
Why?
Can't they protect themselves?
I joined the gang
not to save myself
I joined them
to protect our friends...
To protect the most important person
in my life.
Zein...
it's okay to be angry at me.
But I won't have any regrets about this.
I will never abandon you.
Even until death, Zein.
I won't falter.
- Zein...
- Who's whining in there?
Get out.
Where are you?
There's no point in hiding in there.
Show yourself!
Hurry up.
Zein
We're going to catch you.
whatever happens
I need you to close your eyes.
- Matt, why?
- Get out of there.
Show yourself!
Zein, please.
I need you to trust me.
Just do it, please.
Close your eyes.
Whatever happens
keep them closed.
Show yourself, little rats!
Show yourself!
- Okay?
- Get out of there!
Zein!
- Please!
- Get out!
Stay here.
Please stay inside.
Come on, show yourselves!
He's out. The little rat's out.
Finally!
Are you the new BBG member?
You don't seem so tough now
Why?
Aren't you confident that
your members have your back?
It seems like you joined the wrong gang.
The Devil God Warrior
is the stronger gang here
in Hell University.
Aren't you too full of yourselves?
Why? Planning to fight us?
Why?
You think you can beat me?
Look at this tough guy.
You little shit.
Stand up!
I said stand!
This is the best you can do?
What a weakling.
That's all you got?
Weakshit.
Where's your gang now?
Stand up!
They're over here! Hurry!
Scram!
Get out of here!
Assholes!
Hurry up!
Bunch of bastards.
He's okay.
Let's go.
Who is it?
Matt!
Nurse Cha!
Nurse Cha, he's awake!
He's stable for now.
He's lucky someone saved him.
Are you okay?
Where does it hurt?
- It hurts, Zein.
- What's wrong?
Where does it hurt?
Zein, you're sitting on my arm.
His arm, Zein.
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
Zein, be careful.
I'm sorry, are you okay?
I should be the one apologizing.
Matt...
you don't have to apologize.
Let's go.
Okay.
Zein...
I'm so sorry.
Sorry because
I kept a secret from you.
From all of you.
I'm sorry that I had to hide it from you.
Matt...
I should be the one apologizing.
I’m sorry if
I made a promise to trust you
but I broke it.
Sorry if-
I understand, Zein.
I wasn't hurt by that
but do you know what hurts?
It hurts seeing the woman I love cry.
Matt...
But I know that
someone got to your heart first.
I know it's him.
I'm happy for you.
Finally, Zein...
I don't want to be selfish anymore
and continue fighting for your affection
because I already know that in the end
I won't be the one you'll choose.
But promise me, Zein.
That you'll never cry again.
Just grant me that, Zein.
It'll be enough for me.
Matt...
Zein
promise me
please?
Cause it'll hurt me more
seeing you cry.
So please grant me that promise
that you'll never cry again.
Can you promise me that, Zein?
Promise it to your best friend.
Promise.
How is he?
Thank you.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Matt saved me.
Matt is one lucky guy
to have a friend like you.
Lucky?
I don't think so.
Yeah
He really is.
I want to be as lucky as him one day.
Aren't you afraid, Supremo?
If you lose your position
you can't protect her anymore.
You should be afraid
because I know your secret, Supremo.
Aren't you curious
why Raze has been quiet lately?
Why don't you ask him yourself?
Matt.
The food is almost ready.
You should eat before
they finish all of it.
What can I do for you?
Wow
how polite of you.
I'm hungry.
Aren't you hungry, girls?
Yes.
Take our orders
three plates of pasta
two steaks
and...
drinks?
Do you want any drinks?
I'll have mango.
Strawberry for me.
And I want softdrinks.
Got that?
Make sure it arrives hot, okay?
Hurry up, Queen!
Thanks, queen!
What a way to show her who's boss.
Thank you
I'm not hungry yet.
I'll eat it later, Supremo.
Eat.
I'm not hungry.
And I still have a lot to do.
I'm sure Zein is capable of
eating when she feels hungry.
She's right, Supremo.
Boundaries, remember?
And she still has a lot to do.
Don't you think you're
being too close to her?
Have you forgotten your position here?
I know what I'm doing
but I don't care.
Give us the room.
But, Supremo...
I said
give us the room.
This is outrageous!
I got this for you
from the cafeteria.
I'm really good, Supremo.
And I prefer leafy food compared to meat.
So do you prefer
that I'll feed you bermuda grass?
You need protein, Zein.
Especially if you have a lot
on your plate every day.
Oily food is bad for the health.
It causes heart disease.
Eat it
or else.
Or else what?
I'll eat you.
Happy?
You have no idea.
Incineration protocol.
Copy.
If I'm the enemy
you'd be dead by now.
Are you an enemy, Supremo?
You said you know taekwondo.
Show me.
Why are you staring?
You're good.
But...
Too many openings.
You lack training.
Just so you know
taekwondo isn't the only thing I know.
Maybe you'd like to move your hand away?
I told you
you can look at me
but you're not allowed to touch me.
Too easily distracted.
One wrong move and I will kick your balls.
How can I give you a
baby if you kick my balls?
Fuck you one million times, Supremo!
My assessment?
Too easily distracted and
too out of shape.
Sorry if I'm not sexy enough for you.
I don’t know what ‘sexy’ means for you.
But I just meant you’re too unfit
to defend yourself.
I don’t mind helping you with that.
Okay?
Thank you.
Why did you choose me as your secretary?
You could've chosen someone else.
Like Angelica?
Angelica?
She's not even fit for the position.
Because you don't want
her to have a hard time?
If she finds it hard
it'll be harder for me.
Because you like her?
If she's not able to do her job properly
it'll be troublesome for me.
Look at Fritzy.
She's too vain for the position.
And she can't even
stand the sight of blood.
Not everyone has the capacity
to tolerate blood like you do.
As long as it’s not your blood, I’m good.
You know
this is what I don't like about you.
You'll do everything you can
to save the people you love.
But you can't do it for yourself.
You can't even beg
for me to spare your life.
Because I know it will
affect your position here.
Isn’t it clear to you yet, Zein?
When we saved Ms. Aya and Lyka
I was reprimanded
by Sir Francisco and Madam Violet.
Fuck this position if I can't have you.
But you worked so hard
for this position, Ace.
And I know that it took a lot
from you to get here.
That's why everyone respects you
and follows your command.
Really?
If so
can I give you an order?
What do you have in mind?
What do I have to do?
Any orders from you
I'll do it.
Please give me an order, Supremo.
You must not take an order from anyone.
You'll only take orders from me.
This is an order from the highest
Supreme Student Government.
And you can't do anything about it.
You're ruining everything!
What did I do to you?
You didn't do anything
and you're not going to do anything
except to stay away from Supremo.
Are you nuts?
You don't tell me what to do.
Stay away from Supremo
or you die.
You choose, Zein.
Kill me now.
I'm not going to let you or
Supremo's stupidity ruin everything!
I dare you
to stay close to him.
You'll feel the extent of my rage.
What happened?
Zein
I won't let anything-
I can fight my own battles.
There you go.
Don't touch it and it'll heal on its own.
Thank you.
Is there something between
you and the Supremo?
Even if there is,
it's none of your business.
I'm tired, Zein.
I made a promise
that I'll help heal
everyone who needs it, but
they threatened me.
I'm sorry...
Nurse Cha?
I'm tired of being a pawn to their game.
I know in the end
I won't be able to escape this place.
I also lost hope for my sibling.
The fight isn't over yet.
I won't let them win.
We will escape this place
whether they want to or not.
It's time for me to commit to my promise
to heal everyone who needs healing.
What do you mean?
The night you and your friend got poisoned
I kept something from you.
The poison didn't come from the liquor.
And it wasn't from the plastic you found.
How are you sure?
Because of the symptoms
you and your friend had
is from a chemical compound
found here
in this clinic.
A student requested it from me.
A student you know well.
I know this isn't enough
but I hope this shows how sincere I am.
I wish it could've been someone
else who did this betrayal.
I would've have accepted it
But him?
I'll find out the truth tonight.
Matt
Are you okay?
Zein
I'm sorry again about what happened.
Matt
didn't I tell you
it's nothing.
I'm happy that
there are no secrets left between us.
Just like before.
Yes, just like before.
The hiker girl!
Why do you still remember that?
How can I forget?
You know you think you
were so smooth back then?
Also, you think you were so casual
in asking for her number.
I genuinely thought
it was her dad.
How should I know that was her boyfriend?
You're lucky that I was there.
Oh, really?
If I wasn't there...
If you weren't there
I would’ve been beaten to pulp.
Exactly.
What was her name again?
It starts with L.
What is it again?
Lorraine!
Right!
Her!
Lorraine.
But who got exhausted
during the hike again?
Hey!
You were the one who told me
that we shouldn't bring that up again?
But you were the one who started it, Zein.
Promise me again.
Pinkie promise.
Come on! Game?
You're asking too many questions!
Why don't we just play truth or date?
- He's feeling brave!
- Game!
As long as no one gets offended.
And also remember
to not regret any of it.
You're yapping too much.
Let's just do it.
Mia
Truth or dare.
Dare.
- What?
- Dare?
Kiss.
Hey!
Do you want to get punched?
I'll gladly do it!
I was just kidding!
Let's take this seriously.
How about you sing for us?
You can do it!
Do it, Mia.
It's just your friends here.
Promise we won't laugh.
Do it, please.
Cheers!
Your turn to ask.
Van
truth or dare?
Truth.
Who's your crush here?
That's it!
In this room?
Or in the entirety of Hell U?
The entirety of Hell U, of course.
Wow.
Mia, you're too kind.
Who is it, Van?
No one.
I don't have time to
flirt with anyone, okay?
Boo!
Answer it.
You'll get nothing from me.
Zein, your turn!
Me?
Dave...
Truth or dare?
Hmm...
Truth.
During the acquaintance party
who was your crush that night?
Of course
it's Mia.
He's too smooth with it.
Even if I was drunk
Mia's still the most beautiful.
Aw, she's blushing!
So...
you remember that night?
How could I forget?
I almost died that night.
If so
where did you get the liquor
that poisoned both of us?
Zein
how am I supposed to remember that?
don't be a buzzkill.
How about the ice cubes?
Where did you get it?
What are you insinuating, Zein?
That it was my fault?
I didn't do anything!
Zein!
Stop it!
Perfect timing!
You took the liquor
with the ice
and you returned to the table.
Right?
But wait
you weren't alone, right?
You were with someone.
Do you guys remember?
Do any of you remember?
What are you talking about?
Jerome
where were you that time?
What did you do?
What are you saying, Zein?
Do you remember?
Where did you go that night?
What did you do?
I have a feeling that the stuff
in my bag will fall on the floor.
Pick it up for me.
This is so amusing.
My slaves multiplied.
You are such a disappointment.
This is your last chance, Supremo.
Do what you want.
I already found the source of my happiness
and I don't have any plans to let that go.
Please...
please.
Please breathe.
Help us!
Help!
Please.
You!
Venomancer!
You're going to pay for
what you did to Supremo.
Zein!
MkvDrama.net